[
  {
    "gameNumber": 1,
    "gameRipens": "01/01/2022",
    "gameRotten": "12/31/2022",
    "gameOfTheWeek": [
      {
        "category": "sports",
        "questions": {
          "qOne": {
            "difficulty": 1000,
            "question": "Which sport is not part of the triathlon",
            "correct_answer": "Pole Vault",
            "wrong_answers": ["Running", "Cycling", "Swimming"]
          },
          "qTwo": {
            "difficulty": 2000,
            "question": "In golf, what would a score of two under on a hole be called?",
            "correct_answer": "Eagle",
            "wrong_answers": ["Bogey", "Birdie", "Albatross"]
          },
          "qThree": {
            "difficulty": 3000,
            "question": "Lebron James has won how many NBA Championships?",
            "correct_answer": "4",
            "wrong_answers": ["3", "2", "5", "3.5"]
          },
          "qFour": {
            "difficulty": 4000,
            "question": "In which two states do the most NFL teams play their home games?",
            "correct_answer": "California and Florida",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "Texas and California",
              "Florida and Texas",
              "New York and Texas",
              "California and New York"
            ]
          },
          "qFive": {
            "difficulty": 5000,
            "question": "Which MLB pitcher has the most career strikeouts",
            "correct_answer": "Nolan Ryan",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "Roger Clemens",
              "Tom Seaver",
              "Randy Johnson",
              "Greg Maddux"
            ]
          }
        }
      },
      {
        "category": "geography",
        "questions": {
          "qOne": {
            "difficulty": 1000,
            "question": "What is the capital of the United States of America?",
            "correct_answer": "Washington, D.C.",
            "wrong_answers": ["Philadelphia", "New York City", "Wilmington"]
          },
          "qTwo": {
            "difficulty": 2000,
            "question": "In what country is Stonehenge located?",
            "correct_answer": "England",
            "wrong_answers": ["Ireland", "Portugal", "Georgia"]
          },
          "qThree": {
            "difficulty": 3000,
            "question": "What is the only country that borders the United Kingdom",
            "correct_answer": "Ireland",
            "wrong_answers": ["Scotland", "Denamrk", "Wales", "France"]
          },
          "qFour": {
            "difficulty": 4000,
            "question": "What country has the most natrual lakes",
            "correct_answer": "Canada",
            "wrong_answers": ["China", "Sweden", "Russia", "USA"]
          },
          "qFive": {
            "difficulty": 5000,
            "question": "What mountain range traditionally separates Europe and Asia",
            "correct_answer": "The Ural Mountains",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "The Caucasus Montains",
              "The Baikan Mountains",
              "The Dolomites",
              "The Appalachian Mountains"
            ]
          }
        }
      },
      {
        "category": "tv's & movies & music oh my",
        "questions": {
          "qOne": {
            "difficulty": 1000,
            "question": "Who played agent Fox Mulder on the TV Series 'The X-Files'",
            "correct_answer": "David Duchovny",
            "wrong_answers": ["Ted Danson", "Bryan Cranston", "Tom Selleck"]
          },
          "qTwo": {
            "difficulty": 2000,
            "question": "Who won the first season of American Idol?",
            "correct_answer": "Kelly Clarkson",
            "wrong_answers": ["Ruben Studdard", "Clay Aiken", "Fantasia"]
          },
          "qThree": {
            "difficulty": 3000,
            "question": "What is (most consistently) Homer Simpson's job?",
            "correct_answer": "Safety Inspector",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "Accountant",
              "Civil Engineer",
              "Architect",
              "Astronaut"
            ]
          },
          "qFour": {
            "difficulty": 4000,
            "question": "In what movie does a character in prison talk about a life in Zihuatanejo",
            "correct_answer": "The Shawshank Redemption",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "Con Air",
              "Cool Hand Luke",
              "The Great Escape",
              "The Green Mile"
            ]
          },
          "qFive": {
            "difficulty": 5000,
            "question": "After Beyonc√©, which female artist has won the most Grammys?",
            "correct_answer": "Alison Krauss",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "Aretha Franklin",
              "Adele",
              "Lady Gaga",
              "Alicia Keys"
            ]
          }
        }
      },
      {
        "category": "literature",
        "questions": {
          "qOne": {
            "difficulty": 1000,
            "question": "'A Song of Ice and Fire' is the name a series of novels adapted into what TV show?",
            "correct_answer": "Game of Thrones",
            "wrong_answers": ["The Witcher", "True Blood", "Camelot"]
          },
          "qTwo": {
            "difficulty": 2000,
            "question": "Tweedledee and Tweedledum are from which children's novel?",
            "correct_answer": "Alice Through the Looking Glass",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "Where the Wild Things Are",
              "A Wrinkle in Time",
              "The Little Prince"
            ]
          },
          "qThree": {
            "difficulty": 3000,
            "question": "Who's famous books series features a second book, 'The Two Towers'",
            "correct_answer": "J.R.R. Tolkien",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "C.S. Lewis",
              "J.K. Rowling",
              "D.B. Cooper",
              "E.L. James"
            ]
          },
          "qFour": {
            "difficulty": 4000,
            "question": "Ernest Hemingway wrote 'The Old Man and the Sea' and...",
            "correct_answer": "'A Farewell to Arms'",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "A Brave New World",
              "Ulysses",
              "The Beautiful and Damned",
              "East of Eden"
            ]
          },
          "qFive": {
            "difficulty": 5000,
            "question": "Question",
            "correct_answer": "Answer",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "wrong answer 1",
              "wrong answer 2",
              "wrong answer 3"
            ]
          }
        }
      },
      {
        "category": "category",
        "questions": {
          "qOne": {
            "difficulty": 1000,
            "question": "Question",
            "correct_answer": "Answer",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "wrong answer 1",
              "wrong answer 2",
              "wrong answer 3"
            ]
          },
          "qTwo": {
            "difficulty": 2000,
            "question": "Question",
            "correct_answer": "Answer",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "wrong answer 1",
              "wrong answer 2",
              "wrong answer 3"
            ]
          },
          "qThree": {
            "difficulty": 3000,
            "question": "Question",
            "correct_answer": "Answer",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "wrong answer 1",
              "wrong answer 2",
              "wrong answer 3"
            ]
          },
          "qFour": {
            "difficulty": 4000,
            "question": "Question",
            "correct_answer": "Answer",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "wrong answer 1",
              "wrong answer 2",
              "wrong answer 3"
            ]
          },
          "qFive": {
            "difficulty": 5000,
            "question": "Question",
            "correct_answer": "Answer",
            "wrong_answers": [
              "wrong answer 1",
              "wrong answer 2",
              "wrong answer 3"
            ]
          }
        }
      }
    ]
  }
]
